Guide to the Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000.
Firebrand Books records,
- Series III. Financial Records
  - Invoices #2260-#2309, Mar. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #2310-#2359, Mar. 1987-Apr. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #2360-#2409, Apr. 1987-May 1987 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #2410-#2459, May 1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #2460-#2509, May 1987-June 1987 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #2510-#2559, June 1987 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #2560-#2609, June 1987-July 1987 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #2610-#2659, July 1987-Aug. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #2660-#2709, Aug. 1987-Sept. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #2710-#2759, Sept. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #2760-#2809, Sept. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #2810-#2859, Sept. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #2860-#2909, Sept. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #2910-#2959, Sept. 1987-Oct. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #2960-#3009, Oct. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #3010-#3059, Oct. 1987-Nov. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #3060-#3109, Nov. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #3110-#3159, Nov. 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #3160-#3209, Nov. 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #3210-#3259, Nov. 1987-Dec. 1987 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #3260-#3309, Dec. 1987 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #3310-#3359, Dec. 1987 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #3360-#3409, Dec. 1987-Jan. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #3410-#3459, Jan. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #3460-#3509, Jan. 1988-Feb. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #3510-#3559, Feb. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #3560-#3609, Feb. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #3610-#3659, Feb. 1988-Mar. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #3660-#3709, Mar. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #3710-#3759, Mar. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #3760-#3809, Mar. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #3810-#3859, Mar. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #3860-#3909, Mar. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #3910-#3959, Mar. 1988-Apr. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #3960-#4009, Apr. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #4010-#4059, Apr. 1988 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #4060-#4109, Apr. 1988-May 1988 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #4110-#4159, May 1988 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #4160-#4209, May 1988-June 1988 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Invoices #4210-#4259, June 1988 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #4260-#4309, June 1988 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #4310-#4359, June 1988-July 1988 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #4360-#4409, July 1988 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #4410-#4459, July 1988-Aug. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #4460-#4509, Aug. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #4510-#4559, Aug. 1988-Sept. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #4560-#4609, Sept. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #4610-#4659, Sept. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #4660-#4709, Sept. 1988-Oct. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #4710-#4759, Oct. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #4760-#4809, Oct. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #4810-#4859, Oct. 1988-Nov. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #4860-#4909, Nov. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #4910-#4959, Nov. 1988-Dec. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #4960-#5009, Dec. 1988 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #5010-#5059, Dec. 1988-Jan. 1989 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #5060-#5109, Jan. 1989 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #5110-#5159, Jan. 1989-Feb. 1989 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #5160-#5209, Feb. 1989 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #5210-#5259, Feb. 1989-Mar. 1989 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #5260-#5309, Mar. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #5310-#5359, Mar. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #5360-#5409, Mar. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #5410-#5459, Mar. 1989-Apr. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #5460-#5509, Apr. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #5510-#5559, Apr. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #5560-#5609, Apr. 1989-May 1989 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #5610-#5659, May 1989 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #5660-#5709, May 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #5710-#5759, May 1989-June 1989 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #5760-#5809, June 1989 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #5810-#5859, June 1989 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #5860-#5909, June 1989-July 1989 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #5910-#5959, July 1989 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #5960-#6009, July 1989-Aug. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #6010-#6059, Aug. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #6060-#6109, Aug. 1989-Sept. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #6110-#6159, Sept. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #6160-#6209, Sept. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #6210-#6259, Sept. 1989-Oct. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #6260-#6309, Oct. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #6310-#6359, Oct. 1989 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Invoices #6360-#6409, Oct. 1989-Nov. 1989 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #6410-#6459, Nov. 1989 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #6460-#6509, Nov. 1989 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #6510-#6559, Nov. 1989-Dec. 1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #6560-#6609, Dec. 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #6610-#6659, Dec. 1989-Jan. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #6660-#6709, Jan. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #6710-#6759, Jan. 1990-Feb. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #6760-#6809, Feb. 1990-Mar. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #6810-#6859, Mar. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #6860-#6909, Mar. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #6910-#6959, Mar. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #6960-#7009, Mar. 1990-Apr. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #7010-#7059, Apr. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #7060-#7109, Apr. 1990 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #7110-#7159, Apr. 1990-May 1990 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #7160-#7209, May 1990 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #7210-#7259, May 1990 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #7260-#7309, May 1990-June 1990 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #7310-#7359, June 1990 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #7360-#7409, June 1990 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #7410-#7459, June 1990-July 1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #7460-#7509, July 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #7510-#7559, July 1990-Aug. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #7560-#7609, Aug. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #7610-#7659, Aug. 1990-Sept. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #7660-#7709, Sept. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #7710-#7759, Sept. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #7760-#7809, Sept. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #7810-#7859, Sept. 1990-Oct. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #7860-#7909, Oct. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #7910-#7959, Oct. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #7960-#8009, Oct. 1990-Nov. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #8010-#8059, Nov. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #8060-#8109, Nov. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #8110-#8159, Nov. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #8160-#8209, Nov. 1990-Dec. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #8210-#8259, Dec. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #8260-#8309, Dec. 1990 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #8310-#8359, Dec. 1990-Jan. 1991 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #8360-#8409, Jan. 1991 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #8410-#8459, Jan. 1991-Feb. 1991 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #8460-#8509, Feb. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #8510-#8559, Feb. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #8560-#8609, Feb. 1991-Mar. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #8610-#8659, Mar. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #8660-#8709, Mar. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #8710-#8759, Mar. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #8760-#8809, Mar. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #8810-#8859, Mar. 1991-Apr. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #8860-#8909, Apr. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #8910-#8959, Apr. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #8960-#9009, Apr. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #9010-#9059, Apr. 1991-May 1991 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #9060-#9109, May 1991 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #9110-#9159, May 1991 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #9160-#9209, May 1991-June 1991 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #9210-#9259, June 1991 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #9260-#9309, June 1991 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #9310-#9359, June 1991-July 1991 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #9360-#9409, July 1991 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #9410-#9459, July 1991-Aug. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #9460-#9509, Aug. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #9510-#9559, Aug. 1991 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Invoices #9560-#9609, Sept. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #9610-#9659, Sept. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #9660-#9709, Sept. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #9710-#9759, Sept. 1991-Oct. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #9760-#9809, Oct. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #9810-#9859, Oct. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #9860-#9909, Oct. 1991-Nov. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #9910-#9959, Nov. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #9960-#10009, Nov. 1991-Dec. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #10010-#10059, Dec. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #10060-#10109, Dec. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #10110-#10159, Dec. 1991 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #10160-#10209, Dec. 1991-Jan. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #10210-#10259, Jan. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #10260-#10309, Jan. 1992-Feb. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #10310-#10359, Feb. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #10360-#10409, Feb. 1992-Mar. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #10410-#10459, Mar. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #10460-#10509, Mar. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #10510-#10559, Mar. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #10560-#10609, Mar. 1992 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #10610-#10659, Mar. 1992-Apr. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #10660-#10709, Apr. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #10710-#10759, Apr. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #10760-#10809, Apr. 1992-May 1992 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #10810-#10859, May 1992 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #10860-#10909, May 1992 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #10910-#10959, May 1992-June 1992 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #10960-#11009, June 1992 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #11010-#11059, June 1992-July 1992 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #11060-#11109, July 1992-Aug. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #11110-#11159, Aug. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #11160-#11209, Aug. 1992-Sept. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #11210-#11259, Sept. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #11260-#11309, Sept. 1992-Oct. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #11310-#11359, Oct. 1992-Nov. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #11360-#11409, Nov. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #11410-#11459, Nov. 1992-Dec. 1992 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #11460-#11509, Dec. 1992-Jan. 1993 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #11510-#11559, Jan. 1993-Feb. 1993 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #11560-#11609, Feb. 1993 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #11610-#11659, Feb. 1993-Mar. 1993 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #11660-#11709, Mar. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #11710-#11759, Mar. 1993-Apr. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #11760-#11809, Apr. 1993-May 1993 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #11810-#11859, May 1993-June 1993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #11860-#11909, June 1993-July 1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #11910-#11959, July 1993-Aug. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #11960-#12009, Aug. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #12010-#12059, Aug. 1993-Sept. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #12060-#12109, Sept. 1993-Oct. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #12110-#12159, Oct. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #12160-#12209, Oct. 1993-Nov. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #12210-#12259, Nov. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #12260-#12309, Nov. 1993-Dec. 1993 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #12310-#12359, Dec. 1993-Jan. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #12360-#12409, Jan. 1994-Feb. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #12410-#12459, Feb. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #12460-#12509, Feb. 1994-Mar. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #12510-#12559, Mar. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #12560-#12609, Mar. 1994-Apr. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #12610-#12659, Apr. 1994-May 1994 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #12660-#12709, May 1994 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #12710-#12759, May 1994-July 1994 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Invoices #12760-#12809, July 1994-Aug. 1994 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Invoices #12810-#12859, Aug. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #12860-#12909, Aug. 1994-Sept. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #12910-#12959, Sept. 1994-Oct. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #12960-#13009, Oct. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #13010-#13059, Oct. 1994-Nov. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #13060-#13109, Nov. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #13110-#13159, Nov. 1994-Dec. 1994 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #13160-#13209, Dec. 1994-Jan. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #13210-#13259, Jan. 1995-Feb. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #13260-#13309, Feb. 1995-Mar. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #13310-#13359, Mar. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #13360-#13409, Mar. 1995-Apr. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #13410-#13459, Apr. 1995-May 1995 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #13460-#13509, May 1995-June 1995 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #13510-#13559, June 1995-July 1995 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #13560-#13609, July 1995-Aug. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #13610-#13659, Aug. 1995-Sept. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #13660-#13709, Sept. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #13710-#13759, Sept. 1995-Oct. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #13760-#13809, Oct. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #13810-#13859, Oct. 1995-Nov. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #13860-#13909, Nov. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Invoices #13910-#13959, Nov. 1995-Dec. 1995 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Invoices #13960-#14009, Dec. 1995-Jan. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #14010-#14059, Jan. 1996-Feb. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #14060-#14109, Feb. 1996-Mar. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #14110-#14159, Mar. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #14160-#14209, Mar. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #14210-#14259, Mar. 1996-Apr. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #14260-#14309, Apr. 1996-May 1996 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #14310-#14359, May 1996-June 1996 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #14360-#14409, June 1996-July 1996 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #14410-#14459, July 1996-Aug. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #14460-#14509, Aug. 1996-Sept. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #14510-#14559, Sept. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #14560-#14609, Sept. 1996-Oct. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #14610-#14659, Oct. 1996-Nov. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #14660-#14709, Nov. 1996-Dec. 1996 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #14710-#14759, Dec. 1996-Jan. 1997 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #14760-#14809, Jan. 1997-Feb. 1997 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #14810-#14859, Feb. 1997 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #14860-#14909, Feb. 1997-Mar. 1997 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #14910-#14959, Mar. 1997 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #14960-#15009, Mar. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #15010-#15059, Mar. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #15060-#15109, Mar. 1997-Apr. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #15110-#15159, Apr. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #15160-#15209, Apr. 1997-May 1997 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #15210-#15259, May 1997-June 1997 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #15260-#15309, June 1997-July 1997 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #15310-#15359, July 1997-Aug. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #15360-#15409, Aug. 1997-Sept. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #15410-#15459, Sept. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #15460-#15509, Sept. 1997-Oct. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #15510-#15559, Oct. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #15560-#15609, Oct. 1997-Nov. 1997 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #15610-#15659, Nov. 1997-Jan. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #15660-#15709, Jan. 1998-Feb. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #15710-#15759, Feb. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #15760-#15809, Feb. 1998-Mar. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #15810-#15859, Mar. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #15860-#15909, Mar. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #15910-#15959, Mar. 1998-Apr. 1998 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #15960-#16009, Apr. 1998-May 1998 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #16010-#16059, May 1998-June 1998 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #16060-#16109, June 1998-July 1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #16110-#16159, July 1998-Aug. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #16160-#16209, Aug. 1998-Sept. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #16210-#16259, Sept. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #16260-#16309, Sept. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #16310-#16359, Sept. 1998-Oct. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #16360-#16409, Oct. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #16410-#16459, Oct. 1998-Nov. 1998 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #16460-#16509, Nov. 1998-Jan. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #16510-#16559, Jan. 1999-Feb. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #16560-#16609, Feb. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #16610-#16659, Feb. 1999-Mar. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #16660-#16709, Mar. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #16710-#16759, Mar. 1999-Apr. 1999 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #16760-#16809, Apr. 1999-June 1999 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #16810-#16859, June 1999-July 1999 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #16860-#16909, July 1999-Sept. 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #16910-#16959, Sept. 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #16960-#17009, Sept. 1999-Oct. 1999 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #17010-#17059, Oct. 1999-Nov. 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #17060-#17109, Nov. 1999-Jan. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #17110-#17159, Jan. 2000-Feb. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #17160-#17209, Feb. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #17210-#17259, Feb. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #17260-#17309, Feb. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #17310-#17359, Feb. 2000-Mar. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #17360-#17409, Mar. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #17410-#17459, Mar. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #17460-#17509, Mar. 2000-Apr. 2000 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #17510-#17559, Apr. 2000-May 2000 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #17560-#17609, May 2000-June 2000 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #17610-#17659, June 2000-July 2000 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #17660-#17709, July 2000-Aug. 2000 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #17710-#17759, Aug. 2000-Oct. 2000 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #17760-#17809, Oct. 2000-Nov. 2000 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #17810-#17836, Nov. 2000-Dec. 2000 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: The Distributors, 1987-1991 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Bookslinger, Inc., 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Bookpeople, 1985-1990 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Bookpeople, 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inland Book Company, Inc., 1985-1991 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inland Book Company, Inc. / Inbook, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inland Book Company, Inc. / Inbook, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inland Book Company, Inc. / Inbook, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inland Book Company, Inc. / Inbook, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inbook / LPC Group, Mar. 1996-May 1996 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: Inbook / LPC Group, June 1996-July 1996 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Aug. 1996-Sept. 1996 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Oct. 1996-Nov. 1996 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Dec. 1996-Jan. 1997 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Feb. 1997-Mar. 1997 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Apr. 1997-May 1997 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, June 1997-July 1997 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Aug. 1997-Sept. 1997 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Oct. 1997-Nov. 1997 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Dec. 1997-Jan. 1998 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Feb. 1998-Mar. 1998 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Apr. 1998-June 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, July 1998-Sept. 1998 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Oct. 1998-Jan. 1999 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Feb. 1999-June 1999 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, July 1999-Dec. 1999 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, Jan. 2000-June 2000 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Distributors' Reports: LPC Group, July 2000-Dec. 2000 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Distributors' Reports: Bulldog Books, 1988-1993 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Distributors' Reports: Bulldog Books, 1994-1998 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Distributors' Reports: Airlift Book Company, 1985-1991 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Distributors' Reports: Airlift Book Company, 1992-1996 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Distributors' Reports: Airlift Book Company, 1997-2000 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Distributors' Reports: Banyan Tree Book Distributors, 1998-2001 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Vendor Files: Telephone Services, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Vendor Files: Photography & Manuscript Services, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Vendor Files: Office Supplies, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Vendor Files: UPS, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Vendor Files: Shipping, Maintenance, Legal, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Vendor Files: Telephone Services, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Vendor Files: Photography & Manuscript Services, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Vendor Files: Office Supplies, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Vendor Files: UPS, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Vendor Files: Shipping, Maintenance, Legal, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Vendor Files: Telephone Services, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Vendor Files: Photography and Manuscript Services, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Vendor Files: Office Supplies, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Vendor Files: UPS, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Vendor Files: Shipping, Maintenance, Legal, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Vendor Files: Telephone Services, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Vendor Files: Photography and Manuscript Services, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Vendor Files: Office Supplies, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Vendor Files: UPS, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Vendor Files: Shipping, Maintenance, Legal, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Vendor Files: Telephone Services, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Vendor Files: Photography and Manuscript Services, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Vendor Files: Office Supplies, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Vendor Files: UPS, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Vendor Files: Shipping, Maintenance, Legal, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Vendor Files: Telephone Services, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)